Ben therapist the
REM I don't think the medication's
working I can't maintain an erection
chicks won't talk to me I think I'm
depressed I need more anti-depression
medication Myer work said my work my dap
down you know what I'm
saying I said my Wier won't want to do
is watch porn I want to watch videos of
porn I like watching girls do with each
other that makes my wi happy but it
still work my wi won't work I said my
Wier won't work my dong just flaps
down what
I'm I said my work I think ruin my life
my I'm afraid of everything I'm afraid
of dying the here in my head here
I can't feel emotion ruin my life I
always cry myself to sleep I think I
have a broken heart but I can't feel
this is a waste of my time leave my
mother out of oh boy here we again I
don't keep a journal cuz I'm afraid what
I'll read I cry myself to sleep cry
myself to sleep I can't sleep I can't
wake up I can't wake up keeps going
going going going this is not helping
the medication's not working I think you
charged me twice last week Char me hurts
here in my head hurts here and here I
can't feel emotions I think I ruin my
life